GDSVF\&H\2457598.3

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Unlimited Labs Inc. (“we”, “our” or “us”) on the collection,

use and disclosure of your information on www.unlimitedlabs.com and b12.io (the “Websites”) and the services, features,

content or applications we offer (collectively with the Websites, the “Services”). We receive information about you from

various sources, including: (i) if you register for either Website and the Services, through your user account on the Services

(your “Account”); (ii) your use of the Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the

Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information

as described in this Privacy Policy.

What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) gathered when you

are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our

business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites that we develop or maintain on behalf of our clients, as our clients have sole

control over the privacy policies maintained on such websites nor does it apply to the practices of any other third parties

that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, plug-ins, services and applications

(“Third Party Services”) that you elect to access through the Services or to individuals that we do not manage or employ.

While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot

take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review

the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

What Information Do We Collect?

The information we gather enables us to improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of

the Services, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of

information from our users.

Account Information:

When you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username,

password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account on

the Services and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not

be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services. You may unsubscribe

from these messages through your Account settings, although we, regardless, reserve the right to contact you when we

believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes.

Financial Information:

We do not currently collect financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration

date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing

company (the “Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s

applicable terms of service and privacy policy.

User Content:

Some features of the Services may now or in the future allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written

comments. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your

account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal Personal Information, as

described in this Privacy Policy.

IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically:

GDSVF\&H\2457598.3 2

• We may automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Services,

including your IP address and cookie information. This information is used for fighting spam/malware and also to

facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services (e.g., what links you have clicked on).

• Generally, the Services may automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to

the Websites. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would

identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how

often individuals use parts of the Services so that we can analyze and improve them.

Email Communications:

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer

service.

Information Collected Using Cookies:

• Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a

website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We use cookies to enable our

servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Websites and otherwise use the Services.

• Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information

collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use

cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Services and may associate that information with

your Account if you have one.

• Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new

cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of

each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave cookies active, because they enable you

to take advantage of the most attractive features of the Services.

• This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not

control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link

points may set cookies on your computer.

Information Related to Advertising and the Use of Web Beacons:

To support and enhance the Services, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties to serve advertisements,

through the Services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third

party companies called “ad networks.” Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and

research firms.

Advertisements may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category and may be based on anonymized

information inferred from information provided to us by a user, including Personal Information (e.g., gender or age), may

be based on the Services usage patterns of particular users, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services. We

do not provide Personal Information to any ad networks for use outside of the Services.

To increase the effectiveness of ad delivery, we may deliver a file (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network to you

through the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting

for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit

other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s

servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.

Aggregate Information:

We collect statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Services

(“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information. This statistical information is

not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser.

GDSVF\&H\2457598.3 3

Information Regarding Your Social Networks or Websites:

You may now or in the future be able to use your Account on our Services to interact with your accounts on other services,

such as Facebook or Twitter, or with your owned and operated websites. Please note that these tools are operated by Third

Party Services.

By using these tools, you acknowledge that information from those Third Party Services may be transmitted into your

Account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy.

Additionally, when you use one of these tools, the Third Party Service may be collecting information about your browser or

online activity through its own tracking technologies and subject to its own privacy policy. Last, when you use these tools,

some of your information from the Services may be shared with the Third Party Service and others. Therefore, we

encourage you to read the privacy policies and other policies of the social networks and other Third Party Services you use

in connection with the Services.

How, and With Whom, Is My Information Shared?

Public Information About Your Activity on the Services:

Some of your activity on and through the Services may be public or accessible by members of your project team by default.

Please remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information using certain public features of the Services, then that

information is governed by the privacy settings of those particular features and may be publicly available. Individuals

reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your

knowledge, and search engines may index that information.

IP Address Information:

While we collect and store IP address information, that information is not made public. We do at times, however, share this

information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business, and as otherwise

specified in this Privacy Policy.

Information You Elect to Share:

You may access other Third Party Services through the Services, for example by clicking on links to those Third Party

Services from within the Websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party

Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services’ privacy policies. This Privacy

Policy only governs information collected on the Services.

Aggregate Information:

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business.

We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use our Services and

their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how our Services interface with them. In

addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non Personal Information about you

that they have independently developed or acquired.

Email Communications with Us:

As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive email and other communications from us, such as communications

relating to your Account. Communications relating to your Account will only be sent for purposes important to the

Services, such as password recovery.

Financial Information:

As stated above, we do not currently collect financial information, as that information is collected and stored by our

Payment Processor. However, we may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our

Payment Processor for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, enrolling you in

discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, protecting against or identifying possible fraudulent

transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

GDSVF\&H\2457598.3 4

Information Shared with Our Agents:

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our

control (our “Agents”). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide products or

services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other

information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal

Information with our Agents.

Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the

transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or

enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You

acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal

Information as set forth in this policy.

Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others:

We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as we reasonably believe is necessary to (i)

satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms

of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or

technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public.

This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware

prevention.

Information Shared with Partners

We work with partners and will share information with them so they can communicate with you about products and events

that may be of interest to you and for other promotional purposes.

Information We Share With Your Consent:

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will

be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized

access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting

access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.

We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any

Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the

security of user information at any time.

We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard techniques. We

do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store,

Personal Information or otherwise.

What Information of Mine Can I Access?

If you are a registered user, you can access information associated with your Account by logging into the Services.

Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.

California Privacy Rights: Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us

for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third

parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a

GDSVF\&H\2457598.3 5

California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Unlimited

Labs Inc., 89 5 th Avenue 7 th Floor, New York, NY 10003.

How Can I Delete My Account?

Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by emailing hello@b12.io. If you terminate your Account,

any association between your Account and information we store will no longer be accessible through your Account.

However, any public activity on your Account prior to deletion will remain stored on our servers and may remain

accessible to the public.

What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?

• You can always opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some

of our features.

• You can delete your Account. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account,

and activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us.

What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in

effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you

by posting an announcement on the Services or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy

when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please send us a detailed message to

hello@b12.io. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: May 4, 2018
